My name is Tomaki Sakurai.
I'm just your average student who enjoys his peace and quiet more than anything in the world.
But my best friend is this chick with a vicious karate chop who's always out to get me.
My freak boy classmate thinks he can fly, and if that wasn't enough, I'm getting bombarded with SOS messages in my dreams.
And last but certainly not least, I've got Icarus, some alien chick who fell out of the sky.
The following story depicts the downfall of my peaceful, quiet little life.
Let's get started.
This was when you came up with the past and realized that you became official.
I thought so, it was going so.
I can't hear my heart, bass,止められないよ
The sound of the love that I like, can you hear my heart, bass?
I can't hear my heart, but I can't hear my heart, bass,止められないよ
But I can't hear my heart, but I can't hear my heart, bass,止められないよ
I'm sure you know this, but if you don't, consider this a refresher
The Earth has magnetic lines that run between its northern and southern axes, creating magnetic fields
If this black hole of sorts is causing the fields to become disturbed, well, here's an example
Migratory birds use these fields to travel, it helps them determine direction
Any abnormality in this field will cause the bird to lose sight of its destination and plummet from the sky
So if this is what's going on, then it's possible for something now to be able to fly when before it could not
There's a reason for everything in this universe
Basically, anything that flies has a reason to be flying
What's important is who flies first
That's bad, I'll mark that as a fail
I can't take it if these suckers get any bigger
Tomo, good morning
For crying out loud, is he still asleep?
Tomoki, get your lazy butt out of bed, you're gonna...
Zahara, it's not what it looks like, I swear
I'm just trying to get this stupid chain off, look
What the hell is this? Why the hell is there a chick with wings in your room?
Well, um, she's a...
She just, like, fell out of the sky
Do I look brain dead to you?
There's no way I'd believe a load of punk like that
Why not? It's the truth!
Look at her, Zahara!
Would you freakin' look? She's flying!
See? See? Huh? Huh? Right?
Don't go!
Ah! Zahara!
Forget that chick
I still gotta do something about this heavy-ass chain
I can extend it, as far as you need
Or if you would prefer, I can remove it altogether
Why don't you fill me in on this stuff sooner?
All right, I'm outta here
Yes, master
Zahara!
Would you at least hear me out?
What are you doing?
Don't follow me, Icarus!
Come here!
Really? This is wonderful, Tomuki
I mean, she's obviously an inhabitant of the New World
And how'd you figure that out?
If I remember what Zahara told me
You're currently living alone
Because your parents are touring the countryside
Isn't that correct?
Uh, yeah, that's right
Perfect!
Then you can keep an eye on her
Until we work out the details
This is all for the sake of the New World
You sure you're gonna be okay with this, Tomuki?
You start living with a cute girl like her
Don't you think one thing might just lead to another?
Like, what exactly?
Oh, I don't know
Maybe accidentally tossing her onto your bed
And then your childhood friend sees you rolling around with her
Which rings in the start of a seedy love triangle
Have you been watching us?
Just a woman's intuition
But you know women get way freaked out when they're jealous
Hopefully the bloodshed will stay to a minimum
Jeez! Don't jack with my head like that!
Hey, Icarus, I need you to go home and look after the house
I'm gonna stay here for a while
Master, you should take this
Yeah? What is it?
It's a card like the others, just an older model
Seeing as those others are all gone now
Yeah, another card, whatever
But Master, you need to know
It's cool, I got it
Now when you leave here, go straight home
No stopping on the way, alright?
Alright, Master
What we're really looking at
Man, now this is the life
Peace and quiet really is the best
Being able to enjoy the slightest bit of it is pretty great
Especially with all the crap that's happened in the past few days
Oh yeah, I forgot
She gave me that old card
But I'm not gonna use it
That's way, way too dangerous
I've learned my lesson after the recent disasters
Mmm
But I gotta say
It'd be pretty sweet to have some kind of pervy superpower
Hey Tomo, you wanna go eat outside with me?
I brought along a lunch for you too, cause I'm awesome like that
Thanks, Zohara, I appreciate it
Now, uh, about that girl of yours
Oh, you mean Icarus?
You're really gonna let her live with you?
I'm just kinda playing it by ear
Alright
Wait a minute, you're not pissed at me, are you?
No, I guess I really can't be
You've already made up your mind about the whole thing
So it's not like I can change it
Well, you still seem pretty ticked
And I told you I wasn't
Hey, watch where you're walking or you're gonna...
Yeah, I tried to...
You saw him
No, no I didn't
Was that a picture of a dog?
It's not like Zohara's in elementary school anymore
I wish she'd wear something a bit more grown up or something
You gotta be kidding
Dude, those are panties
Flying frickin' panties
Hang on, those look familiar
Toma Key
Why the hell is your pocket glowing?
No way
The card, it did this
It did this
Such a moron
If you'd stop and think for a second, I didn't do anything
The card acted all on its own
Your BS explanations can wait
I have to find some underwear to put on fast
Sugata, mind if I borrow your room for a little bit?
Wanna fill me in?
This whole day is balls thanks to this stupid-ass card
What?
This is so screwed up
What the hell is going on?
I know Tomo's always been a pervert
But this is off the deep end
Are you all right? Zohara?
This doesn't look good
This is screwed
Why the hell is this happening?
Doesn't matter what she puts on her bottom half
They all just fly away
Interesting
And this card seems to be the culprit behind the sordid affair
What the hell, Toma Key?
Why can't you put an end to this screwed up fantasy?
I'm doing what I can
Why don't you try putting this on?
Okay, but what is that?
It's a mawashi
Why would she wear that?
Please tell me that's not yours
I have almost everything you would want in this room
And since you're playing dress up, you might as well try it all
Red bikini bottoms
Fishnet stockings
Medical gauze
I understood the other things, but the gauze was just weird
It doesn't look like anything seems to be working
And it's not limited to undergarments either
She looks like she's having a real tough time
Whose big damn fault do you think that is?
I'm sorry, all right? Don't freak out
I have a feeling master is in danger
Looks like my gym shorts didn't work either
I don't want to play anymore
Gosh, Zahara
What if you can't ever wear panties for the rest of your life?
Wow, you're giving that an awful lot of thought
I'm not thinking about anything
I didn't realize you were into fetishy stuff
So is all this going according to your dastardly plan?
I don't have any plan
We can't rule out that possibility though
If this card grants unconscious wishes
It could have read your thoughts and did what you wanted
So let's run an experiment
What do you say?
Try using this card to wish for something else
Yeah, all right
Handcuffs
Are you kidding?
I get it
What are you doing?
Phew
What the hell?
Just something I've always wanted to try on you
Tomaki, you listen
I'm not wearing anything under my skirt right now
And if the wind blows through here
Can you tell me how you expect me to hold my skirt down?
Can you?
Are you in danger, master?
I'm not
Master
Panties
I
Huh?
I need them
I need panties right now
You need panties, understood
I will amass all panties within a hundred meter radius
What?
Oh
This month I've got four projects that I...
No!
Mikuko, what happened?
She got me
My panties, they're wrong
It's so warm and moist
Will this be enough panties for you, master?
Yes, now please make it stop
Stop!
I caught all of our panties
And they're flying
Listen up, sonny boy
I want you to heed your old grandpa's words
When you're a hunting bird
Shoot the first one that takes flight or you're in trouble
Cause once the first one goes
The rest are all gonna follow after
So make damn sure you shoot down the first one that gets his ass in the air
Never forget that piece of advice, kid
First in the air, shoot his ass
Icarus, could you explain all of this to us? Is this because of the card?
Correct, this card is nothing more than a teleportation device used to send order requests for various things to the synapse
It is an older model card, so it only has the power to grant the request for a single wish
In this particular instance, the card involved managed to forcefully grant my master's wish
Well, finally, this whole situation's starting to make sense, mystery solved
What do you mean, mystery solved?
Let me explain
Here's the premise
Tomaki didn't like the panties he saw when you bent over
For whatever reason, they weren't his cup of tea
Because of this powerful emotion, the card activated and forcefully removed the panties he detested so much, sending them off into the ether
Those handcuffs are simply another tool, giving him the ability to force you to do as he wishes
You've got a hidden little deviant side there, don't you, Tomaki?
My opinion of you is improving all the time
It's not me, it's that freaking card, I swear
So you gonna tell me what I gotta do to make all this crap stop?
Now that we know the cause, the solution should come rather simply
All you have to do is put on the underwear Tomaki wants you to wear
We just need to get Icarus and Mikako to buy as much underwear as they can find
Get something sheer, a girl should always feel kinda sexy, you know
So I got no choice but to try every single pair on one by one?
I guess my top priority though is to get home without incident first
You just leave all of that to me
I've got you covered all the way back to your place, nothing's gonna surprise me
Are you kidding me?
Looks like someone upstairs has it in for you
You'll be able to see up my skirt in the reflection
Don't worry, I'm on it, my brain has a genius plan
Raleigh Flop!
You might wanna flip over, genius
Tomo, whatever you do, just make sure my skirt doesn't fly up or I'll have to kill you
Atomic manners!
Oh!
Here we go! Gentleman's Speed Kick!
Zibaree!
Tomaki's getting serious
He's surpassing all his normal human abilities
I'm back
We bought panties, master
Whoa! You got a crap ton!
With this, Manny, I'm sure we've found at least one that's going to suit Tomoki's tastes
Hopefully
Well, why don't we get started?
I'm gonna need both of you girls to help me out if it's cool
I can't do anything with these on
Sure
We can do this!
So, what do you think about these? They're pretty cute
Tomoki might dig the whole satin thing
Gotta start somewhere
Oh, Icarus, I'm sorry, but can you help me out?
Yes, miss
Here you go
Be careful, Icarus! You're tickling me! You're gonna make me go all...
I'm sorry, I didn't mean to
It's fine, I guess I am the one making you help me out
Hope I'm not making it too hard on you
No, miss, it's no problem at all
You're a nice person, you know that?
I can't thank you enough, Icarus
Well, crap, that didn't work
How about trying on this frilly pair next?
They might be playing up the innocent vibe too much, but who knows?
What is your freakin' problem, Chomo? There was a pile of panties and none of them worked?!
Don't tell me you want me to go commando for the rest of my natural life?!
Pervert
Hey, shut up! That's not it at all, but you should at least consider the possibility!
Which is?
Living life without panties!
Pardon me, Miss Sohara, I found one more pair obscured under the bag
No way those'll work! They're practically the same pair that started this whole god-awful disaster!
I see
But I might as well give it a shot. What if I got to lose, right?
So, uh, those didn't work?
I know we just met, but it was nice knowing you
No! You can't leave me here alone!
No, they weren't!
Huh?
They're on! I'm wearing them right now!
And look, the handcuffs came off too! Pretty great, huh?
Awesome! So it's finally over?
That's correct. This card shut itself down without any errors, so everything should be fine now
Oh, thank god
Really? That's not very comforting
You said yourself they're pretty much the same underwear you started this whole business with
I didn't think about that yet, but yeah, you're right
Who freaking cares?
In fact, I don't want to think about panties for a long, long time
You and me both, Tomo
I'm real sorry about today, Sohara
Oh, it's cool. Everything worked out in the end
Yeah, but Icarus didn't give me that card to start trouble
In fact, just the opposite
Yeah, I know. Don't worry about it
So, it, uh, looks like you and Icarus are gonna be living together for a while, huh?
I guess. It's not like I can leave her alone. She'd be kinda screwed
And she's got no place else to go
Plus, I feel bad with her having to walk around with that collar around her neck
That sounds just like you
Oh
I don't know
You've always been like that
When you were little, you'd bring home lost dogs
You'd prattle on about how sad it was they had these collars
So you'd take them off
No matter how long it took to cut through them, you'd do it
That's just part of what makes you such a sweet person, Tomo
You know?
Uh, forget about that last part
Speaking of the past, those dog panties you had on
Guess you haven't really changed either
What?
You don't remember? How could you forget?
Tomo, I can't! No matter how hard I try, I can't do it! I'm too weak! I can't chop through something this big!
You can't do it because you don't have enough spirit, you idiot! Try harder!
I'm trying! I'm trying! I'm trying! I'm trying! I'm trying! I'm trying!
Now it's time for some Spartan training!
There!
Hey, check out the cute puppy dogs!
Gotta love panties with designs on them!
And that was the day you realized what you were capable of
The day your killer chop first surfaced
So that's what must have happened to me
That's the day I stopped liking dogs
It's all flooding back
Yeah, that makes sense
No wonder I hated your dog panties so much
You're saying I had to go through with that nightmare because of your stupid childish issues?
Then all of this was your fault after all!
Tomo, you freaking idiot!
Tomo!
ute
Thank you.
This is News at 11, our top story.
Around the world, extremely rare panty meteor showers have been reported.
Some experts have cited abnormal weather for causing this phenomenon, but many organizations
are still investigating.
Several of these showers have been spotted here over the skies of New York, which has
brought about concern that this spectacle could cause problems.
In response, cabinet members have been flooding the White House.
As for now, the best we can do is wait and see what our president and his supporters
plan to do to combat this growing problem.
Next time, Angeloid Directive Zero.